[{"id":"6016","question":"<p>Who among the following earns Rs. 35,000?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"A","option2":"L","option3":"B","option4":"K","option5":"N","correct_option":"N","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:48:07","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p><img src=\"file:\/\/\/C:\/Users\/admin\/AppData\/Local\/Temp\/msohtmlclip1\/01\/clip_image001.gif\" style=\"height:207px; width:3px\" \/>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>C<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 18,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>D<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;K<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 23,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;L<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;A<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>N<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 35,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>B <\/strong>&rarr;&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>N earns Rs. 35,000.<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6015","question":"<p>Who among the following earns the highest?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"B","option2":"N","option3":"A","option4":"L","option5":"K","correct_option":"B","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:47:46","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p><img src=\"file:\/\/\/C:\/Users\/admin\/AppData\/Local\/Temp\/msohtmlclip1\/01\/clip_image001.gif\" style=\"height:207px; width:3px\" \/>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>C<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 18,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>D<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;K<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 23,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;L<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;A<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>N<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 35,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>B <\/strong>&rarr;&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>B earns the heights&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6006","question":"<p>What is the code for economics?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"ab","option2":"ka","option3":"ha ","option4":" ja      ","option5":"Either \u00e2\u20ac\u02dcka\u00e2\u20ac\u2122 or \u00e2\u20ac\u02dcha\u00e2\u20ac\u2122","correct_option":"Either \u00e2\u20ac\u02dcka\u00e2\u20ac\u2122 or \u00e2\u20ac\u02dcha\u00e2\u20ac\u2122","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:42:56","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>demand&rarr; de<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>and &rarr; pa<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>supply &rarr; re<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>market &rarr; ni<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>needs &rarr; fe<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>more &rarr; ja<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>is &rarr; le<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>related &rarr; ab<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>to &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>economics &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>The code for &lsquo;economics&rsquo; is either &lsquo;ka&rsquo; or &lsquo;ha&rsquo;.<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6014","question":"<p>Who among the following earns more than K but less than A?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"C","option2":"N","option3":"D","option4":"L","option5":"B","correct_option":"L","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:47:02","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p><img src=\"file:\/\/\/C:\/Users\/admin\/AppData\/Local\/Temp\/msohtmlclip1\/01\/clip_image001.gif\" style=\"height:207px; width:3px\" \/>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>C<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 18,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>D<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;K<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 23,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;L<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;A<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>N<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 35,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>B <\/strong>&rarr;&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>L earns more than K but less than A.<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6012","question":"<p>Who among the following earn(s) more than Rs. 23,000 but less than Rs. 35,000?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"Only A       ","option2":"Only L        ","option3":"A and L     ","option4":"K and L     ","option5":"A and K","correct_option":"A and L     ","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:46:02","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p><img src=\"file:\/\/\/C:\/Users\/admin\/AppData\/Local\/Temp\/msohtmlclip1\/01\/clip_image001.gif\" style=\"height:207px; width:3px\" \/>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>C<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 18,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>D<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;K<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 23,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;L<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;A<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>N<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 35,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>B <\/strong>&rarr;&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>A and L earn more than Rs. 23,000 but less than Rs. 35,000<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6008","question":"<p>What is the code for more?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"fe   ","option2":" ni        ","option3":"de ","option4":"ja","option5":"Cannot be determined ","correct_option":"ja","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:43:52","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>demand&rarr; de<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>and &rarr; pa<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>supply &rarr; re<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>market &rarr; ni<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>needs &rarr; fe<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>more &rarr; ja<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>is &rarr; le<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>related &rarr; ab<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>to &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>economics &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>more &rarr; ja<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6007","question":"<p>Which of the following represents &lsquo;supply related market&rsquo;?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"ab ni de       ","option2":"ni re ab        ","option3":"pa ni re     ","option4":"de ab ni      ","option5":"None of these","correct_option":"ni re ab        ","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:43:23","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>demand&rarr; de<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>and &rarr; pa<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>supply &rarr; re<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>market &rarr; ni<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>needs &rarr; fe<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>more &rarr; ja<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>is &rarr; le<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>related &rarr; ab<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>to &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>economics &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>supply &rarr; re<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>related &rarr; ab<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>market &rarr; ni<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6009","question":"<p>Which of the following may represents &ldquo;market needs more consumers&rdquo;?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"fe ja ni sa    ","option2":"ja ni de ab         ","option3":"ni ja ka pa       ","option4":"pa ni fe re ","option5":"le re ni ja","correct_option":"pa ni fe re ","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:44:27","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>demand&rarr; de<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>and &rarr; pa<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>supply &rarr; re<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>market &rarr; ni<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>needs &rarr; fe<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>more &rarr; ja<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>is &rarr; le<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>related &rarr; ab<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>to &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>economics &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>market&rarr; ni<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>needs &rarr; fe<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>more &rarr; ja<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>The code for &lsquo;customers&rsquo; may be &lsquo;sa&rsquo;<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6010","question":"<p>What is the code for &lsquo;needs&rsquo;?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"ni ","option2":"fe   ","option3":"pa  ","option4":"le   ","option5":"None of these","correct_option":"fe   ","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:44:45","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>demand&rarr; de<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>and &rarr; pa<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>supply &rarr; re<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>market &rarr; ni<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>needs &rarr; fe<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>more &rarr; ja<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>is &rarr; le<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>related &rarr; ab<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>to &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>economics &rarr; ka or ha<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>needs &rarr; fe<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"6013","question":"<p>Who among the following may earn Rs. 21,000?<\/p>\r\n","option1":"K","option2":"D","option3":"L","option4":"C","option5":"N","correct_option":"D","qa_date":"2016-02-15 15:46:41","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p><img src=\"file:\/\/\/C:\/Users\/admin\/AppData\/Local\/Temp\/msohtmlclip1\/01\/clip_image001.gif\" style=\"height:207px; width:3px\" \/>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>C<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 18,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>D<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;K<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 23,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;L<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp; <strong>&nbsp;A<\/strong> &rarr;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>N<\/strong> &rarr; Rs. 35,000<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>&nbsp;&nbsp; <strong>B <\/strong>&rarr;&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p>D earns more than Rs. 18,000 but less than Rs. 23,000. So, D may earn Rs. 21,000.<\/p>\r\n"}]